Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford Collection 0013.123.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
- Series XXXI: Special Projects/2012/Hartford North End Project II
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Korobochko, Bina, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Krant, Lena, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Livshits, Sarra, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Medovy, Yakov, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Militskiy, Michael, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Murakovskiy, Israel Mura, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Peskin, Vladimir, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Polyakov, Boris, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Prokopets, Ides, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Reker, Michael, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Rozovsky, Yefim, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Sandal, Maryam, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Simkhovich, Izya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Toger, Yakov, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Treyster, Milya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Tseytlin, Zhemya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Yacob, Olga, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Zeygerman, Yosif, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Witnesses/Kogan, Hyman (Chaim)/Autobiography dictated to volunteers, undated
- Series XXXII: Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English Note: these files also contain release forms
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Aronov, Mark, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Aronov, Nina, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Besnosov, Mikhail, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Blekhman, Lyusya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Bratslavsky, Anna, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Domnich, Genya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Frenkel, Mariya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Freydzon, Gdal, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Gelman, Seman, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Grabarnik, Lazar, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Greydinger, Boris, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Gupper, Naum, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Izikson, Abram, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Kaganovich, Israel, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Kaplan, Vladimir, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Khaimova, Esafir, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Kogan, Hyman, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Korobochko, Bina, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Krant, Lena, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Leykikh, Frima, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Livshits, Sarra, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Lundina, Roza, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Medovoy, Yakov, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Metlitsky, Michael, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Murakhovskiy, Israel, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Pekar, Michael, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Peskin, Vladimir, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Polyakov, Boris, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Prokopets, Lida (Ides), undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Rozovsky, Yefim, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Rytman, Dora, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Rytman, Julius, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Sandal, Maryam, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Simkhovich, Izya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Toger, Ykov, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Treyster, Milya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Tseytlin, Zhenya, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Virkerman, Anna, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Yacub, Olga, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Zeygerman, Iosif, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Administrative, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Brochures and Flyers, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Exhibition Labels, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Materials, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Materials (2), undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Script, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Script (2), undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Venues, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Finances, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Grants, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Grants (2), undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Media, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/News Clippings, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Opening Exhibit (JCC), undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Photographs, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War/Release Forms, undated
  - Special Projects/Witnesses/Kogan, Hyman (Chaim) Autobiography, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War, Miscellaneous, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War, Miscellaneous, undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War, Videotapes Special Projects/1998/Witness to War/ Videotapes/Three large record center boxes of videotapes, now (July 2005) stored in archives room (where Farming and Immigration Collections are stored) under glass shelves., undated
  - Special Projects/Witness to War, Miscellaneous, undated
- Scrapbooks
  - 2 boxes of scrapbooks Publicity, exhibits and other scrapbooks, undated
  - Zoosman, Michael/History of Conservative Movement, undated